Hello everyone, my name is Akash Bansal and today I'm
going to be talking about developing accessible digital resources for
children with special needs.
So first we're going to talk about overview and before
that let me share the slides with you. So the
slides of the session are available at HTTPS: slash slash
Akashdeep Branson AKA SH DEPBANSAL dot GitHub GITHUP dot IO
slash.
NCERT 22 slash OK.
Your session with the session could slide up in the
system before you want to be the wrong. Maybe update
this user here.
OK, configuration to you like you want high contrast mode
or something like that, so.
One correct answer that you can follow along with me.
OK.